http://www.platypusmultimedia.com/index.php/privacy-policy

HomeServices
Web Site DevelopmentMultimedia DevelopmentGraphic DesignWeb Site HostingClientsPublishingNewsContact UsContact InfoSupport
Privacy Policy
This is the web site of Platypus Multimedia Solutions.Information is only collected to provide usage statistics.
With respect to cookies: We use them only to improve users' browsing experience.
Links to Other Web Sitesplatypusmultimedia.com site includes links, some temporary and some permanent, to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy and security practices of any other web site or the nature of the content contained therein.Children's PrivacyNone of the content and information in the platypusmultimedia.com web site is targeted toward children under 17 years of age. We make every effort possible to ensure that we do not collect or maintain information on our web site from those we know to be younger than 17 unless parental consent has been obtained in writing.Changes to This PolicyIn the event that Platypus Multimedia decides to alter its privacy policy, the changes will be added directly to this statement. We will, however, always use information in accordance with the version of the privacy policy under which it was originally collected.Contact UsIf you have specific questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at the following address:
8 Old Post RoadNorth Easton, MA 02356We can be reached via e-mail at  This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
back to top
Motivation
Regard it as just as desirable to build a chicken house as to build a cathedral.
— Frank Lloyd Wright
Platypus Multimedia © 2020 - privacy policy
Touch Base
Platypus Multimedia8 Old Post RoadNorth Easton, Massachusetts 02356
Telephone:
Tweet
